Welcome!
Every time I pass by here,
I smell such lovely flowers!
I've been so curious!
As have I.
Shizuka-san, please pick
a flower you like.
What? I'm allowed to pick?!
Yes, of course.
What will it be?
H-How about... roses?
We happen to have wonderful roses today.
Really?!
Well, then... we'll take three.
All right.
Darling, wrap these up!
Sure thing, honey.
They'll be taking these.
He's a big guy!
Sure.
He sounds like he's high up...
Are you married?
Yes. I'm human,
and my husband is an oni.
We have an interspecies marriage.
An interspecies marriage...
and we're an interspecies couple...
YAKO - TONOME
That's right. You're the one who always
stops in front of our shop, right?
I-I'm sorry I never come in...
Hey, it's fine. We're
happy you stopped by today.
Here you are.
The baby's breath is on the house.
Why, thank you!
It's amazing that he can wrap
flowers with those huge hands...
Where in the office shall I place them?
I can't wait to see.
Thank you for coming!
Maybe on the table?
Yes, because it's the center of the room!
The office is instantly transformed
into a healing space!
That reminds me.
Have you always liked roses?
Oh, well...
I've taken a liking to them
since you gave me one, Akira-san.
You can say the most incredible
things off the cuff, Shizuka-san.
Well, let's put them on the table, then.
Yes, of course!
Wh-What just happened?!
Sorry!
It's because I kicked the tree.
Oh, I'm sure it's not.
You can't make a sound like
that just by kicking a tree.
What are you talking about?
Can't you tell from the horn?
You're from a species with horns?
I actually can't see.
Oh, that explains that.
Hold out your hand. I'll help you up.
Of course!
You're very strong, aren't you?
Thank you for your help.
I'm an oni-human mix.
Oni are strong, but I'm still pretty bad
at controlling my strength.
May I ask why it is
that you kicked a tree?
I was feeling frustrated.
I was playing with friends, and...
I only meant to tap her,
but I still go too hard sometimes.
I don't wanna play if I'm just gonna
make people cry, so I slipped away.
How cool! Like a lone wolf!
I'm really not.
But I don't think isolating yourself
is really a good solution.
But... what should I do, then?
Let's see...
Yu! Where have you been?
We looked everywhere!
It's her fault for crying and say
she didn't wanna play with you, right?
It's Yu's fault!
Yeah, he made you skin your knee...
L-Listen...
How about we use this?
A cattail?
I can tag you with it and not hurt you.
L-Like this.
Well?
Well, I guess that's okay.
That'd help with my claws, too.
Let's all use them for the game!
But it'll be hard to notice
we've been tagged with those.
That's true.
How about making bundles?
Yeah, I've got rubber bands!
I'm back!
Welcome home!
I just can't get a handle on it.
What's up, Tonome-chan?
Hey, it's that guy again!
Yes, my client believes
someone's smuggling
their product to sell
on the black market.
He's one of the suspects.
Hey, hey! Did my curse come in handy?
Well, he didn't do anything
suspicious that day.
So it didn't matter at all?!
Excuse me!
Welcome. Is that you, Yu-kun?
Yeah! Hi, Yako-oneechan!
Hello!
Thanks for having me today!
What's all this?
He's interviewing us about our jobs.
For school, apparently.
Yes.
We run an agency,
so let me introduce you to the staff.
He's someone you know?
He's the son of a florist
couple we've gotten to know.
Okay!
Tonome-san, this is Yu Kemauchi.
He'll be learning about our office today.
Nice to meet you!
It's a pleasure.
I'm Tonome, the head detective here.
Is something the matter?
Nothing.
I was thinking I've seen this guy.
You have?
Yeah.
I was playing with my friends
and he yelled at me like,
"You can't be here!"
Was it a dangerous area?
Do you remember where you were?
Yeah.
I see. This area, eh?
So what kind of job do
you do, Yako-oneechan?
Yes, most likely.
I handle the office finances
and manage everyone's schedules.
I'll scope it out.
If we catch him
in the act, we've got him.
Won't it be dangerous?
I'll arrange an escort.
Yako-san.
I'm heading out.
Take care!
Hey, are they going to the place I said?
I couldn't say!
Yako-oneechan, thanks for the interview.
Is that all you needed?
I'm sure Jarashi-san will be
back any minute now...
Nah, it's fine.
I'm heading home.
Later!
I'm gonna tail this detective!
It's my chance to see what
the job's really about!
I'll get a great report out of this!
I know. I'll get pics too!
Huh? He's gone!
I just lost sight of him for a second!
What the...
Was that Yu-kun?
I sensed someone following me...
I didn't think he'd come after me.
That's not safe. I'll get some
distance and change my route there.
Now, then...
So it's somewhere around there?
How much are we shipping?
Too much at once'll be suspicious.
We'll have to break it up.
When's payment?
There he is.
After receipt. I'll hand it
over after it checks out.
That must be the group he's selling to.
I want one lump sum at the end.
This is my chance
to catch him in the act.
Got it.
The shift changes today
are evening and late night.
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
Slippery little brat...
C'mere!
I-I wasn't doing anything!
I was just looking for something!
I didn't do anything wrong!
This little brat
was taking pictures of us!
Y-Yu-kun...
Sneaking around the area, too.
I wasn't doing anything!
Hey, we can't let those pics get out.
I just remembered!
He was hanging around here
yesterday as well!
Hey, someone send you to spy on us?
No!
This little brat's pretty strong...
Yeah, he's an oni. Be careful.
That's right. If I struggle
too much, I could hurt them!
Hey, he settled down.
Take his phone and lock
him in the back room.
C'mon, now.
I deleted the pics
on his phone. What now?
Let's contact the execs for now.
What about the boss?
He'll be here soon.
This is getting out of control.
What do I do? What's
going to happen to me?
Well, what can you do?
We can sell this kid for good money!
No, let's throw him
in the ocean so he can't tell no one!
Shut up! Quit crying!
Pipe down already!
Are you all right?
No need to worry. I've called for backup.
I'll show you a little bit of myself.
Sorry.
S-So cool!
I can't see him, but...
Maybe I'll be a detective when I grow up!
Yeah, this ain't great.
Right? We should probably
pass on the word...
Got it.
Hello? Well, we've got
a little situation here...
I'll untie you now.
Sure!
So?
They say leave the kid and move shop.
Seriously?
Hey, hurry it up!
Sure thing.
Darn it. What a pain in my neck...
It's dark!
What do we do? I can't see anything.
W-Wait just a minute.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad the detective is here.
He's like a superhero!
Hey, what made you want to
become a detective?
Oh, well...
A long time ago, something happened.
I wanted someone to find me.
But nobody was able to,
and it made me very sad.
So I became a detective to find
other people who want to be found.
Got it! And that's why you found me, too!
I'm getting a call.
Sure!
Akira-san?
Are you all right?
I've made it in, and I'm with Yu-kun.
Yu-kun?!
Is he all right?
Yes. He wasn't harmed.
Thank goodness!
Say...
Yes?
Could you keep talking to me?
Just to... distract me.
Well, then...
Long, long ago, in a land far away...
Why a fairy tale?!
Well, it's not easy to just keep talking!
Sorry, sorry. A fairy tale is fine.
I'll start over, then.
Long, long ago, in a land far away,
there lived an old woman and an old man.
The old man went to punch the mountain.
Take that!
The old woman went
to the river to race a peach.
You can't keep up with me!
Those two sound like they're
in rather good health.
The peach was their victory prize.
For what?!
Hey, Yako.
Oh, right!
I forgot to mention it, but Jarashi-san
and Karma-san just arrived!
Should we check on the kid?
Nah.
And the stuff on the second floor?
We're getting it down now.
Sure.
Hey! What are you doing?!
I just feel so weak...
What's with you?
I dunno! It just hit me.
Anyway, let's hurry.
What do we do?
Should I head out ahead
once we've got a full load?
Yes, please do.
Right.
Kikira, is the tracker working?
Yeah.
In that case...
I can hunt down these
child kidnappers myself?
Yeah, just keep it under control.
Let's just get it finished.
Yeah, before the truck comes back—
Who're you?
If you give yourselves up quietly...
I'm willing to show mercy.
Crap. The jig's up.
Oh, is that how we're doing it?
No mercy needed, then?
Damn!
You okay?!
Why, you...!
S-S-Sorry! Forgive me! Mercy, please!
Pathetic.
If you wanted to apologize,
you shouldn't have started with me.
I said you could give
yourselves up quietly.
You really thought I'd
apologize, you brute?!
Why the hell do embezzlers have guns?!
Watch it! Watch it!
Take that and that and that and that!
Die!
Wasting my damn time.
There we go.
You wait up!
Just sit still!
Catch me if you can! So long!
You're not going anywhere!
Takes some guts to try to escape me.
Dummy!
Stop it!
I told her to keep it under control.
The light's on!
Found you!
You hurt, kiddo? You cry?
I'm fine! And I didn't cry!
For reals?
Where's Jarashi-san?
She beat the crap outta the bad guys.
Awesome!
I'll tie him up. Go get Jarashi-san.
Yessir!
I just heard quite a sound!
Are you all right?!
I'm fine.
Your distraction let me relax
until I had to spring into action.
Your fairy tale was a big help.
You're welcome!
Are Yu-kun and everyone else okay?
Yes. We'll all be heading back soon.
Roll, acorn, roll. Roll, acorn, roll.
Oh, there it goes, right into the lake...
Huh?
Which way was it again?
That's... the moon?
Did you just say something?
Ah... Why am I lying on your lap?
I suggested it, since you seemed tired
from everything today.
Come along! Everyone's
gone home, so let's indulge!
I've always wanted to
be someone's pillow!
Well, just for a while.
How long was I asleep?
About fifteen minutes, I think?
Did you just... kiss me?
That was very sudden...
Was that... what I've only read
about in romance novels...
A real grown-up kiss?!
A-Akira-san...
I want you by my side forever.
Aki...
I-I feel the same way.
Good evening!
Tonome-san!
Eh?
Wh-What is it?
Thank you so much
for helping my son today!
What?
Oh, not at all!
Hey, Yu! You have
something to say, right?
Right!
I-I'm sorry for causing
you trouble today!
Not at all. I appreciate your help...
We're very sorry to intrude.
Oh, you didn't!
I'll leave our gift to you outside!
R-Right.
L-Let's go home.
Right.
We've become like regulars at this bar!
We have been here quite a few times.
The first time we came,
I imploded on alcohol a little, but...
I have no romantic experience!
I thought that was charming, though.
Wipe it from your memory.
Actually, when I first
invited you on a date,
there was something
that worried me, too.
Because I'm older, and I'm your boss...
I thought you might feel like you
couldn't say no. That I coerced you.
I absolutely didn't!
Well, I realize now that
it was an unfounded fear.
It certainly was!
Actually, I've felt like
the childish one around you lately.
You aren't! You've
helped me out a lot, too...
I mean... I want us to be
able to rely on each other.
Yes. So...
I want to make it official.
Official?
It's not that I haven't thought
about it before, but...
Shizuka-san.
I'd like us to date with
the goal of marriage.
Marriage?!
Is that a problem?
No, not a problem!
I want us to get married! We will!
Well, not just yet.
We won't!
You answered so quickly.
I'm not nervous anymore, at least.
After all, I want it to always
be your hand that's guiding me.
For now, shall we make plans to cohabit?
We're cohabiting?!
Not just yet.
EPISODE 7: I WANT YOU BY MY SIDE
But let's start planning for it.